(Shedon:)Which leads me to my answer.
(Shedon:)I would choose the ability
(Shedon:)to read people's minds.
(Penny:)Well, I can't read
people's minds.
(Penny:)Actually, that's not true.
(Penny:)I can read men's minds.
(Penny:)But only 'cause it's
usually the one thing.
(Sheldon:)When are we going
to get robot eyes?
(Penny:)You're all alike.
(Sheldon:)Well, what I meant was...
(Sheldon:)I often misinterpret
(Sheldon:)how others are feeling.
(Sheldon:)Like, I can't always tell
if someone is only joking
(Sheldon:)or laughing at me.
(Sheldon:)You know, like, uh, if they're
mad at something I've done
(Sheldon:)or just in a bad mood.
It-it's incredibly stressful.
(Penny:)Really? You always
seem so confident.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not.
(Sheldon:)And if I could read
people's minds,
(Sheldon:)life would be so much simpler.
(Penny:)Well, now I wish I had
(Penny:)the ability to make
that stuff easier for you.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.